ILGWU Justice Photographs 5780/102 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NY Supreme 23-25 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Includes: Workers at Roberts New York were in high spirits as the manned the picketline during a nine-day strike against the firm, Nov. 1979; VP Jay Mazur, Manager of Local 23-25 addresses leaders of the Korean community in New York who visited the local office recently, July 1980; Educational class at ILGWU, no date; Anne and Irving Shulman, Aug. 1980; Italia Bowers, Consuelo De Las Cuenas, Carolina Suarez, Aug. 1980; Local 23-25 retiree club president Rose Stein, and Mike Romano, Aug. 1980; Local 23-25 retirees club with Education Staffer Carmen Marcial, Aug. 1980; Edgar Romney, Local 23-25 Assistant Manager, addresses workers at Midway Hospital Supply Co., fighting for their right to ILGWU representation, Jan. 1981; Two men hang posters advertising a union rally, July-Aug. 1982; Asian woman speaks at a rally, July-Aug. 1982; Local 23-25 rally against Apartheid, June 1986; 20,000 people turn out for rally, filling Columbus Park, no date; Asian women, June 1981
- NY Supreme 23-25, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 18, Folder 14)
- NY Supreme 23-25, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Local 23-25 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Includes: Members of Local 25 on strike against the Marvel Undergarment Co, Brooklyn, 5/15/63; On picketline outside Marvel Undergarment Co., Yolanda Gonzalez holds daughter Olga, with Ida Alama, Dolores Doneda, Beatrice Presley and Marie Pair, no date; VP Shelley Appleton, Manager of NY Local 23-25 presents check in amount of $2500 for Cuban refugee relief to VP Charles S. Zimmerman, General Manager of Dress Joint Council in his capacity as Executive Board member of the International Rescue Committee, with staffer Lydia Vargas, Assistant Manager Jay Mazur, local co-chairman Carrie France, staffer Kathy Andrade, and Gerald Grossman, Supervisor of Local's Blouse Department, 11/1/66; Local 23-25 staffer Ben Fee conducts English class Chinese-speaking ILGers, 12/15/68; Asian woman and daughter, 5/1/68; Mrs. Herbert Lehman, no date; Six Asian women, 5/1/68; VP Shelley Appleton, manager of New York Local 23-25, presents $10,000 check to Salim Jourbran, representative of Histadrut, Israel Labor Federation, with Charles Kriendler, retired Local 25 manager in whose honor the center will be named, and Carrie Franco, Local co- chairman, 8/15/68; Local 23-25 member Lee Chow Wai Ching received two maternity benefits from VP Shelley Appleton, Local Manager, wished King T Chu much happiness in retirement, 3/15/71; Ching Ang Yeung and Ng King Hang, workers at Dynasty Manufacturing in New York's Chinatown, on strike, 12/1/70; Cesar Chavez, director of the United Fur Workers' Organizing Committee speaks at meeting of Local 23-25 shop chairmen and chairladies, with VP Shelley Appleton - Local Manager, Carrie Franco, Local chairlady, and Jay Mazur, Assistant Manager, n.d.; Andrew Imuten, VP of United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, presents scroll to ILGWU VP Shelley Appleton, Manager of New York Local 23-25, 9/15/70; Sportswear Local 23-25 members show off finery made from ILGWU union label material during participation in traditional Easter Parade, Fifth Avenue, New York City, 5/1/74; VP jay Mazur, Manager 23-25, accepts award on behalf of the local for service to the Chinatown community, with Benn Tomm, member of the Board of Directors of the Chinatown YMCA, Dec. 1981; A Local 23-25 member and her child were among the scores of New York City ILGers who joined a protest against Reagan budget cuts last month in Foley Square, no date; VP Jay Mazur, Local 23-25 Manager, congratulates one of the local's 50 textbook scholarship winners, with Executive VP Frederick R. Siems, Sept. 1982; VP Shelley Appleton, Local 23-25 Manager, bestows his best wishes and gratitude to Carrie Franco, local chairlady, who retired after more than three decades of union service, no date; Employees of DY Sportswear in New York City proudly display their backpay checks totaling over $6,000, Local 23-25 Manager and VP Edgar Romney distributed the checks with Business Agent Alice Tse at the local's office, 9/10/85; Congratulating Local 23-25 Scholarship winner, Education Director Kathy Andrade, VP Edward Schneider - Sportswear Joint Board General Manager, VP Evelyn Dubrow - Legislative Director, and Manager Edgar Romney, Sept. 1984
- Local 30 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Includes: London-born ILGers Henry Bayrock examines sample of new style he created for Cesarani, 4/15/77
- Local 32 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Includes: VP Julio Ramirez, manager of New York Local 32, reports at a chairladies meeting, 10/11/74, VP Julio Ramirez, Manager of local 32, presents demands for new corset and brassiere agreement to representatives of the employers' association, at opening of negotiations, with Executive VP Wilbur Daniels, 10/1/74; Local 32 member in chilly spring weather on picketline at Character Foundations plant in New York City, 4/15/75; VP Julio Ramirez, manager of New York Local 32, presents check for holiday backpay to some members who work at Lido Foundations, 10/1/75; Workers at Bestform plant went out on strike in support of 800 Bestform workers in Johnstown, PA, Long Island City, 2/10/75; Executive VP Wilbur Daniels and VP Julio Ramirez, Manager of New York Local 32, shake hands as Ramirez commends Daniels for his major contributions to renewal of Local 32 agreement, 1/1/75; Members of New York Local 32 hear VP Julio Ramirez, manager of the Corset and Brassier Workers' Local, discuss terms of their new agreement, with Executive VP Wilbur Daniels, and Assistant Manager Seymour Simmons of Local 32, 1/1/76; Christmas comes early for workers of Lilyette Brassier Co., who are shown in New York Local 32 office receiving checks for damages awarded on the basis of lack of full employment at the shop, VP Julio Ramirez, '32' Manager greets worker Florence Zammetti, with Business Agent Larry Birch, Robert Harper, office manager, and Assistant Manager Seymour Simmons, 11/1/5/75; President Sol C, Chaikin speaking to New York Local 32 chairladies, with VP Julio Ramirez, manager Local 32, Chairlady Anna Danna of the '32' Executive Board, and '32' Assistant Manager - Seymour Simmons, 10/1/75; At the first of his political discourses at major shops, Vice President Julius Ramirez, Manager of New York Local 32, discusses the issues with workers at Marcus and Wiesen and urges them to vote for Carter-Mondale ticket, with Asst. Manager Seymour Simmons of Corset-Brassiere Local, 10/15/76; Chairladies and other representatives of New York Local 32 members give a $2,461 check from members' contributions to aid victims of the recent Guatemala earthquake, with Alice Clemmer of Milady, Business Agents Mike Cuervas and Sophie Bueno, Gilbert Cawley, public relations representative and Father Terrence J. Mulkerin, Assistant Regional Director, both of Catholic Relief Services which received the check for distribution to Guatemala, VP Julius Ramirez, Manager of Local 32, Assistant Manager Seymour Simmons, Rafeala Fernandez of Figure Flattery, Erna Trayan of Vanity, and Marion Sumpter of True Balance, 4/15/76; VP Julius Ramirez speaks at the annual dinner-dance of the Spanish Labor Committee at the Statler-Hilton Hotel, with Local 144 VP Frank Perez, President Henry Van Arsdale of New York Central Labor Council, Manager Manuel Gonzalez at Dressmakers Local 22 - committee treasurer, Mrs. Ramirez, President Sol C. Chaikin and Jose R. Enzo - Special representative of Mayor Beame, 1/1/77; VP Julius Ramirez manager of New York Local 32, addresses members before he and others in his administration were re-elected by acclamation at the Statler-Hilton Hotel, with Assistant Manager Seymour Simmons of the Corset and Brassiere Workers' Local 32, presents $600 check, representing double paternity benefit to Archer family for birth of twins Tischa and Kischa, parents are Teresa and Jeffrey, a Local 32 member who works at Figure Flattery, 4/15/77
- Local 38 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Includes: Manager Jack Hochman of New York Local 38 tells the Local's Ladies' Tailors, Alteration Worker and Theatrical Costume Workers that their merger with Locals 22 and 89 is a "good and healthy move, " 1/21/75
- Local 40 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Includes: Henry Schwartz, manager of New York Belt makers' Local 40, died, 7/1/72; Following Gerald Grossman's election as new Local 10 Manager, Belt makers; Local 40 elected Richard Sanfilippo as new Manager and Robert Brown as assistant Manager, with Sol Sussman, Secretary to Executive Board, and Angelo Cicatto, local chairman, no date; Members of New York Belt makers' Local 40 are given a change of scene during a recent picnic at Rockland County, New York, 8/1/74; Manager Gerald Grossman of New York Belt makers' Local 40 congratulates Chairlady Alice Sereo as she turns in a 100 percent voluntary contributions collected from workers at Charles Belt for the ILGWU Company Committee Fund, with Business Agent Morris Fishbein, 9/1/74; Organizer Robert Brown releases with S. Kopel workers after ratification of first Local 40 agreement at the Belt shop in Brooklyn, 12/15/74; Members of New York Local 40 receive from Business Agent Sol Goldberg their checks for a 2 percent vacation benefit, 1/15/75; Polyform Plastics workers await physical exam at Union Health Center, 3/15/75; Local 40 manager Gerald Grossman submits for approval demands the union will be seeking in current negotiations with ladies' belt employer, 4/15/76; Local 40 manager Gerald Grossman explains terms of new agreements in men's and ladies' belt shops to membership meeting, with Local Chairman Angelo Ciccatto and Sol Sussman, secretary to Executive Board, 6/15/76; Manager Richard Sanfilippo of NY Belt makers Local 40, receives award from Kurt Lewin of Deborah and Edgar Bergman, director of Belt Industry Committee for the hospital, at fund-raising dinner, no date; Workers at FDR Industries, a belt shop in lower Manhattan, picket to protest employer's unfair labor practices, 2/15/77; Local 40 members approve resolution at recent nominating meeting to elect candidates by acclamation, with Manager Richard Sanfilippo, 2/15/77; ILGWU Assistant President Gus Tyler chats with Local 40 members following his presentation at Ramapo College seminar on multinational corporations with Clark Everling of the college's Labor Studies Program which held the seminar, Local 40 Manager Richard Sanfilippo, Education Director Delroy Scott, Business Agent Lucy Rodriguez, Nancy Scott, Morse Colon, Violet Granum and Sarah Randall, 5/1/77
- Local 48 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Includes: Italian Consul General Vittorio Cordero di Montezemolo pins medal on VP E. Howard Molisani designating him as Grand Official of the Republic of Italy, the Italian Consulate, New York, 5/1/66; John A. Volpe, US Secretary of Transportation, presents a plague to ILGWU First President E. Howard Molisani in recognition of his contributions to school in Abruzzi, Italy, erected in Local 48's name by his father Eduardo, 5/15/69; First Vice President E. Howard Molisani, manager of New York Local 48, speaks out against Soviet restrictions on Jews at a noon Garment Center rally held by the Conference for Soviet Jewry, 9/15/72
- Local 48 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Includes: Local 48 Manager Salvatore Cubisino receives congratulations from President Louis Stulberg and other ILGWU officers at a dinner in his honor, with first Vice President E. Howard Molisani - General Manager of the New York Cloak Joint Board, '48' Education Director James Gurrieri who served as master of ceremonies, General Secretary-Treasurer Sol C. Chaikin, Executive VP Wilbur Daniels, VP Salvatore Noto - Local 89 Manager, VP Edward Schneider - Local 91 Manager, 1/18/75; Manager Salvatore Cubisino of Local 48 made a report to their Executive Board meeting at the local's Brooklyn office, with First Vice President E. Howard Molisani - Cloak General manager, Joint Board Secretary-Treasurer Sol Berger, and '48' chairman John Lomonaco, 1/1/75; Local 48 Assistant Manager Nicholas Bonasera receives medal honoring him as "Cavaliere dell 'Ordine of Republic of Italy" from Italian General Counsel Alessandro Cortere De Bosis at ceremony in honor of Mgr. Bonasera, 12/1/76; Manager Salvatore Cubisino of New York Local 48 welcomes retirees to the first meeting of the Local's Golden Ring Club, with Local Assistant Manager Nicholas Bonasera, Max Schwartz of the council of Golden Ring Clubs, and Education Director James V. Garrieri, 8/1/76; Negatives from Local 48 Nick Bonasera retirement dinner, Dec. 1981
- Local 62 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Includes: Local 62 members who never got their high school degree take a class taught by an instructor from the New York City Board of Education which leads to a high school equivalency degree, 10/1/74; Cecile AcKnel of New York Local 62 Education Department, who has been certified as a registrar, helps a shopper register to vote at the local's booths in front of Korvette's in New York's Herald Square, with Niles Murphy of "New York Votes," 9/1/74; Eneida Gonzalez, who works a Cin-Mod in New York, receives a check for $201.59 in backpay from VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of New York Local 62, 8/15/74; Some of the 135 members who enjoyed a trip to Pennsylvania's Amish Country, arranged by New York Local 62, 8/3/74; At a membership meeting, New York Local 62 members wave their hands to show their full support of demands to be made for a new three year agreement, with VP Matthew Schoenwald, 4/1/75; VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of New York Local 62 helps with toy distribution of party for members' children, 1/15/76; Jerry Schoen, New York Undergarment Local 62 Secretary, presents checks for damages to former Adbelnoor Chairladies, Tina Carruba and Elvira Gioioso, 12/1/75; New York Appellate Court Justice Theodore Kupferman charms audience of New York Local 62 members at their annual end of season party, 8/15/75; New York City Councilman Carter Burdent explains operation of the city council to Local 62 citizenship and high school equivalency class, 7/1/75; President-Elect Sol C. Chaikin addresses ILGers at June 25, 1974 membership meeting of New York Local 62, with VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of Local 62; members of New York Local 62 Golden Ring Club volunteer to survey prices in neighborhood supermarkets after Eileen Hoats with Eileen Hoats, addressing them at a meeting, 11/1/75; Products made by ILGWU retirees at arts and crafts classes conducted by New York Locals 62 and 91 are part of an exhibit now on display at the Board of Jewish Education of Greater New York, with VP Edward Schneider, Manager of Local 91, and VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of Local 62, 7/1/76; New York Local 62 members wave backpay checks totaling $1,032.80 received from Myron Lee Fashions after the shop went out of business and still owed them two weeks pay, with VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager Local 62, Business Agent, Anna Ancana, Amelia Romero, Paola Rineldi, Joseph Zaitt, Jean Reres, Mazie Scarimbdo, Angelina Romeo, Crescenza Pinto, Rosa Failla, Vincenzo Borsa, and Susan Passalogua, 5/1/76; Gerret Rubres, who retired March 1 as New York Local 62 education director, receives good wishes from VP Matthew Schoenwald, '62' manager and activists Willie B, Smith, Dolores Franklin and Rose Hodderich, 4/1/76; Members of New York Local 62 signify their approval of proceedings during the nomination meeting at Roosevelt Auditorium, with VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager '62', 2/15/77
- Local 62 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Includes: VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of Local 62-32, tells shop chairperson about the New Blue Cross family medical coverage plan for all members at the Intimate Apparel Workers Local, 11/25/80; Prince and Broadway, no date; Manager Matthew Schoenwald addresses overflow meeting, 7/15/60; Members of New York Undergarment and Negligee Workers; Local 62 vote in their local elections, 3/1/62; ILGers prepare to board airplane for New York Local 62's sponsored trip to Israel, 7/1/62; Julio Ramirez, Gerel Rubien, Mayor Robert F. Wagner, 10/1/62; Local 62 demonstration, 9/15/63; Auditorium of people, 7/15/63; Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of NY Undergarment Workers' Local 62 hears membership enthusiastically ratify new 3-year contract, Manhattan Center, 8/1/63; ILGWU Legislative Representative Evelyn Dubrow, speaking at NY Undergarment Local 62 Chairladies meeting, 5/1/64; Picket line outside sample shop and showroom of Campus Girl, Inc. at 152 Madison Avenue, NY with member of NY Undergarment Workers' Local 62 Warner Lanny, shop chairman, Julius Ramirez, local organizer, and Simon Cooper, business agent, 3/1/65; Local 6 voter registration, no date; At Local 62 dinner honoring Secretary Isidore Schoenholtz, 9/15/65; With all 45 workers of the Angel wear Manufacturing Co. maintaining a round-the-clock strike Vice Presidents Matthew Schoenwald, Undergarment Workers' Local 62 Manager, and Alberto Sanchez, Organization Director in Puerto Rico, 9/15/65; Picketing of Stella Undergarment Corp. in New York, 11/13/65; VP Matthew Schoenwald, Manager of NY Undergarment Workers Local 62 holds several checks prior to distributing them to former workers of Gramercy Mills, with Kitty Molinelli, 11/1/66; Members if Undergarment Workers Local 62 employed at Style Undies in Queens, NY take an important break to receive flu shots from Dr. Uy as part of the local's annual preventive medicine program with VP Matthew Schoenwald, Local 62 Manager, Francis Christie, shop chairlady, and Business Agent Milton Schaffer, 10/15/67l; Union officials and manufacturers' representatives gathered in President Louis Stulberg's office to sign recently negotiated three-year renewal pact for Local 62, with Abe Dolgen - Local 10 manager, Robert Rosenfeld - Negligee Manufacturers' Association President, Irving Dintz - Allied Underwear Association President, VP Matthew Schoenwald - Local 62 Manager, Abraham Jaffin - Lingerie Manufacturers; Association of New York VP, Jack Gross - Executive Director and Counsel for the Lingerie and Negligee Associations, Billy Weiss - Local 10 Assistant Manager, Elias Liberman - Union Attorney, Jack Rosenbaum - Executive Director Allied Underwear Association, Isadore Katz - Union Attorney, Jerry Schoen - Local 62 Secretary, 7/15/69; Workers at Local 62 meeting acclaim Wagner as he enters Felt Forum, 6/4/69; VP Matthew Schoenwald, Local Manager, 6/5/69; Hand vote gives unanimous approval to outstanding contract, 6/4/69; Friends and family surrounded Mabel Fuller as Undergarment 62 honored her on occasion of her retirement as Educational Director, with Assistant President Gus Tyler, with message from President Louis Stulberg, and Manager Matthew Schoenwald, Mr. and Mrs. Edward Harris, and Mr. and Mrs. Ralph West, no date; VP Matthew Schoenwald, Local 62 manager, bestows best wishes upon Julio Ramirez, who was local director of organization, at farewell dinner for the latter, who has been elected manager of Local 32, with Mrs. Ramirez, no date
- Local 66 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Includes: Murray Gross, Manager of Local 66 and national chairman of the American Veterans Committee with other American Veterans Committee members discusses upcoming Congressional Legislation with President Kennedy, 7/15/62; UN Ambassador Adlai E. Stevenson is presented with the first Dag Hammerskjold Memorial Award of the American Veterans Committee by Murray Gross, national chairman of the organization and Manager of Local 66, 5/1/62; Auditorium of people, no date; During exhibition of painting by members of NY Local 66, Jasper Peyton, who is chairman of organization's civil rights unit, discusses his "still life" with Local Manager Murray Gross, no date; Murray Gross, Manager of New York Embroidery Workers Local 66, with members of the United Labor Congress in Lagos, Nigeria, with Maida Springer, at AFL-CIO Department of International Affairs, 5/1/65; In a moving ceremony labor columnist Victor Riesel thanks NY Local 66 Executive Board members for honoring him and his father, Nathan Riesel a founder of the Embroidery Workers' Local, with his wife, Max Silverberg - Chairman of Local, VP Murray Gross - Local manager, and attorney Robert Markewich, 12/1/66; Among the graduates if recent Local 66 Leadership Training Institute receiving diplomas from VP Murray Gross, Local manager, and Jasper Peyton, Educational Director, are Susie Romer, Georgina Buitrago, Maria Louisa Rivera, Rebecca Fleiss, Nancy Mazzola, Clavon Overstreet, Hilda Camacho, Josefina Valentin, and Blanche Tobias, 5/15/66; Weekly Local 66 art class conducted by Jasper Peyton, Local Education Director and Board member of International Friends Art Guild of Greater New York, with Jennie Horowitz, Marisa Kuriata and Katie Jenks, 3/1/66; VP Murray Gross, New York Local 66 manager, at start of contract renewal negotiations with employer representatives, no date; Members of NY Local 66 where paintings were among 10 prizewinning canvases selected by a panel of judges at the Local 66 Art Show: Annis Bare lift, Lucy Gonzalez, Shirley Goldman, Caroline Behrens, 4/1/67; Members of New York Local 66 employed at Metropolis Button Works eagerly reach for applications for the local's blood bank, with Annunciata Marshall - shop steward, Eleanor Davis, Jasper Peyton - Local Education Director, Mattie White, Juanita Cerezo, Virginia Wilson, Mary Harris, Marie-Therese Chassagne, Therese Sojous, Denise Krause, Myrtle Steward, Sallie Anderson, Olympia Soloman, Bessie Fluellen and Afrodizia Figueroa, 9/15/67; President Louis Stulberg congratulates William Schwartz on his election as new manager of Local 66, succeeding VP Murray Gross, who returned to Dress Joint Council as Associate General Manager, with Roman Bielen, Local Chairman, who presided at Executive Board meeting on 9/26/69; Bwy Local 66 class at High School of Fashion Institute in new York with Gloria Maldonado, Local 66 Education Director who will teach another session of class at local office, Manager William Schwartz, and Mike Malone - Board of Education instructor and Local 66 member, 3/15/71; Local 66 members jammed Hotel New Yorker ballroom to overflowing to hear Manager William Schwartz, with Frank Pantano, local assistant manager, no date; Members of Local 66 learn to improve their skills at machines installed in a classroom at the local's headquarters, with Manager William Schwartz at the Embroidery Workers Local and Education Director Gloria Maldonado, 10/1/73
- Local 89 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Includes: New York Local 89 chairladies learn the details of the new dress agreement at a recent meeting as Manager Frank Longo explains the contract terms with Alfred Rupolo - Manager of Bronx-Harlem District, Nat Lewis - Manager of the Popular Price Dress Department, Manager Longo of Local 89, and Business Agent Tony Claudiano, 4/1/76
- Local 89 (Box 19, Folder 4)